[Script Info]
Title:Amaburi BD 03 sc
Original Script:CASO&SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正兰亭准黑_GBK,44,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,15,1
Style: op_ja,Source Han Sans Bold,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: op_zh,思源黑体 CN Bold,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: ed_ja,Source Han Sans Bold,40,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: ed_zh,思源黑体 CN Bold,40,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,35,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.06,0:00:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管穿什么都帅呆了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.34,0:01:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H34332E&\bord0\pos(640,265)}今天临时停业
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.68,0:01:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs34\bord1\blur3\3a&H80\pos(1020,715)}{\fad(500,1000)}挽救措施没用！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.38,0:02:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江西也!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.56,0:02:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上给我取消
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.43,0:02:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取消什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.31,0:02:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临时停业
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.99,0:02:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没必要听你的指示
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.38,0:02:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游乐园开业29年来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.73,0:02:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从来没有发生过毫无预告就停业的事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.11,0:02:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛辛苦苦积累下来的信赖
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.96,0:02:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然  你竟然!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.42,0:02:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.00,0:02:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  能看见了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.93,0:02:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.52,0:02:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次换我出手了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.97,0:02:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.19,0:02:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前装式的火枪为什么能连发
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.88,0:02:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫夫路卿  冷静点
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.04,0:02:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静不下来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.13,0:02:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将毫不知情的来宾撵回去这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.19,0:02:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么失礼的事情是不可原谅的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.00,0:02:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先从外观下手
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.96,0:02:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都从这里开始
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.96,0:02:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别胡扯了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.08,0:03:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚上任的地上人  知道这个游乐园的什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.71,0:03:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的也有一定道理
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.82,0:03:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你就负责去招待来宾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.93,0:03:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么样的表演都没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.83,0:03:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在正门前的广场  你去招待来宾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.76,0:03:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里什么都没有  要怎么做…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.80,0:03:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做不到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.14,0:03:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然做得到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.64,0:03:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就等着看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.63,0:03:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维护做得很到位
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.98,0:03:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只臭老鼠  工作上还是挺能干的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.20,0:03:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江同学  需要检查的地方还有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.91,0:03:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.78,0:03:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都到齐了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.02,0:03:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么现在开始部长会议
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.72,0:03:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长话短说  目前有三个课题
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.10,0:04:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先第一个  延长营业时间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.39,0:04:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别抱怨  你们是小孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.83,0:04:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  问题在于延长多久
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.43,0:04:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那里没有夜间营业的设备
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.65,0:04:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最多也就能延长到日落而已了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.58,0:04:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.63,0:04:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先将关门时间从五点推迟到七点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.14,0:04:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时开始布置夜间营业的设备
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.97,0:04:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,设备到位后时间延长到九点  就这么定了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.84,0:04:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.49,0:04:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二个  休息日全部取消
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.43,0:04:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没完啦  给我差不多一点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.68,0:04:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了周五休息  你们到底想不想干了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.64,0:04:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是愉快的周五啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.57,0:04:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.76,0:04:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个屁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.13,0:04:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才正是捞钱的时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.39,0:04:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  明天开始到7月31日为止
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.55,0:04:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有一天假期  明白了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.48,0:04:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.86,0:04:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.97,0:05:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第三个  这个最关键
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.23,0:05:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到7月31日为止
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.32,0:05:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门票以及所有的娱乐设施全都免费
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.64,0:05:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.70,0:05:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.05,0:05:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从经理的立场来说  我反对
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.97,0:05:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢性赤字的本游乐园没有这样的资本了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.74,0:05:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水电都要花钱的啊  小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.73,0:05:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都是职业的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.24,0:05:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能免费去表演
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.14,0:05:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你职业表演殴打客人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.87,0:05:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候是我的错啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.26,0:05:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不管是什么样的表演  免费是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.44,0:05:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要免费过一次  以后再想收钱就难了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.18,0:05:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦如此  就彻底完了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.32,0:05:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也料到会被反对的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.25,0:06:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的意见都很有道理
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.31,0:06:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.71,0:06:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就统一定为30日元吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.98,0:06:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定为30日元有什么依据吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.97,0:06:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这座游乐园明年就是30周年了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.99,0:06:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就以这个名义
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.26,0:06:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算收30日元  跟免费也没有太大区别
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.21,0:06:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起赤字  现在重要的是客流量
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.73,0:06:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达不到目标的话  以后的赤字也不用谈了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.47,0:06:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  今天的会议到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.94,0:06:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都回自己的岗位去  解散
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.40,0:06:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,30日元  30日元啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.73,0:06:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.20,0:06:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小鬼  说我们的表演就值30日元啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.72,0:06:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.08,0:06:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生气也没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.58,0:06:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马卡隆你不生气吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.14,0:06:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吧  反正没有来宾的话我们就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.89,0:07:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在只能不择手段了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.27,0:07:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上台了  点心妖精
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.88,0:07:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是啊  音乐妖精
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.93,0:07:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦  转换心情  去迎接来宾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.91,0:07:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少烦人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.23,0:07:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想去的是出岛乐园啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.31,0:07:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法只能来这里结果居然停业
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.87,0:07:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我道歉  你个山寨货
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.94,0:07:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉  客人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.00,0:07:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小武住手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.67,0:07:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是孩子的母亲吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.50,0:07:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢您来阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.88,0:07:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种玩偶很多人都摸来摸去的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.96,0:07:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能染上奇怪的病菌所以不能摸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.44,0:08:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.56,0:08:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是小武出什么事了  我就投诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.15,0:08:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好觉悟哦  山寨货
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.09,0:08:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欺凌表演来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.84,0:08:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是火上浇油啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.78,0:08:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  是对您宝贝孩子的担心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.56,0:08:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.25,0:08:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.00,0:08:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么啊  完全不能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.03,0:08:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说还能说话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.68,0:08:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.12,0:08:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.68,0:08:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.47,0:08:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被这家伙欺负了  真心受不了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.97,0:08:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然对客人施加暴力  真是没常识啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.39,0:08:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来教育教育你  把玩偶装脱掉  山寨货
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.52,0:08:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人就是上帝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.32,0:08:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而就算是上帝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.02,0:08:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嘟囔什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.97,0:08:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有不能触碰的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.59,0:08:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这表情算什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.10,0:09:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不揍你你就不明白是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.35,0:09:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.57,0:09:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.97,0:09:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.76,0:09:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃我一拳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.88,0:09:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  搞砸啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.19,0:09:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  那个玩偶不是一般人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.75,0:09:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘  装作没看见
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.33,0:09:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就在这睡着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.40,0:09:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就轮到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.93,0:09:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我是山寨货的人的结局
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.04,0:09:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就亲身体会一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.74,0:09:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好觉悟吧  客人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.37,0:09:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不住手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.52,0:09:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Forgotten  Realms  消除记忆的子弹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.33,0:10:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就会醒过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.09,0:10:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯罪  这是犯罪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.73,0:10:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你马上就会适应了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.88,0:10:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不想适应
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.71,0:10:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.85,0:10:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然对客人施与暴力  真是闻所未闻
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.43,0:10:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是被传出去  马上就完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.82,0:10:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.75,0:10:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也知道错了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.35,0:10:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该不会平时就在这么做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.92,0:10:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.69,0:10:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多每年都会搞砸一次
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.84,0:10:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真亏你能做到现在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.67,0:10:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  抱歉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.02,0:10:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要想开除我的话请随意
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.74,0:10:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙  知道自己的立场才这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.06,0:10:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下不为例
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.48,0:10:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次就放过你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.56,0:10:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再出问题的话就直接开除
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.88,0:10:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我记好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.69,0:11:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你会开除它
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.67,0:11:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是四棒打者
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.67,0:11:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且因为你的子弹  总算把事情处理了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.50,0:11:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  关于这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.81,0:11:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.20,0:11:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个Forgotten  Realms是非常贵重的子弹
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.42,0:11:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做一颗要耗费一年时间
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.09,0:11:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数量有限  请注意
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.18,0:11:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然是这么贵重的东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.47,0:11:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着  那个超疼的子弹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.62,0:11:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你整天都在用啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.96,0:11:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Painbringer吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.23,0:11:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个的话30日元10颗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.02,0:11:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好便宜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.90,0:11:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  有些东西不能随意使用
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.38,0:11:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才帮大忙了  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.13,0:11:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.88,0:11:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做的事情我都会做的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.00,0:11:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那这就请你为此脱衣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.36,0:12:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到真的要脱衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.64,0:12:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳衣有点打擦边球呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.97,0:12:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被性骚扰中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.64,0:12:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿这种泳衣出去  脑子坏掉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.15,0:12:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想看看男性版
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.55,0:12:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,树型姿势
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.64,0:12:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西尔菲  翅膀定住了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.04,0:12:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个能拿下来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.04,0:12:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  毕竟是服装嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.83,0:12:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,服装?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.03,0:12:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  好一个破坏别人梦想的游乐园啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.87,0:12:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江大人  拍我这样的真的没关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.21,0:12:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.47,0:12:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如说能拍到你求之不得
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.38,0:12:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.08,0:12:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起喊  一  二
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.62,0:12:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘城光辉游乐园  票价全部30日元
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.06,0:13:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再精神一点  一  二
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.31,0:13:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘城光辉游乐园  票价全部30日元
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.48,0:13:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉媞珐  笑容太僵硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.06,0:13:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再放开点  一  二
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.12,0:13:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘城光辉游乐园  票价全部30日元
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.28,0:13:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千斗  你那根本不叫笑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.23,0:13:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.49,0:13:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘城光辉游乐园  票价全部30日元
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.51,0:13:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个能行  能行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.07,0:13:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鄙人特利戈  不由自主身体前倾了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.17,0:13:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都在计划之中呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.06,0:13:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  莫夫路居然会允许拉媞珐大人出演呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.93,0:13:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.52,0:13:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  你不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.37,0:13:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫夫路是拉媞珐大人的…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.53,0:13:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江西也!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.75,0:13:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻停止
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.50,0:13:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.51,0:13:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下流的宣传
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.49,0:14:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没必要听你的指示
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.47,0:14:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然那样对待拉媞珐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.33,0:14:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.28,0:14:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.46,0:14:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  果然看得见
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.87,0:14:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.68,0:14:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.96,0:14:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是这个模式
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.82,0:14:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫夫路卿  请冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.91,0:14:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我冷静?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.00,0:14:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉媞珐身体不好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.12,0:14:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然穿成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.38,0:14:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饶不了你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.12,0:14:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体不好?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.27,0:14:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我有说过不愿意的话可以不做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.29,0:14:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真的是一个好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.60,0:14:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能会拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.63,0:14:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你利用了她这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.17,0:14:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.24,0:14:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公主殿下是知晓了一切才答应的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.64,0:14:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.09,0:14:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让我再重复
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.06,0:14:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再继续胡闹会令公主殿下伤心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.98,0:14:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.41,0:15:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是尽可能不要把她带出空中庭园
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.86,0:15:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里是结界
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.06,0:15:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然明白
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.27,0:15:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结界?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.97,0:15:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要告诉三个月后就要离开这里的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.88,0:15:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公主殿下由于一些原因
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.69,0:15:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不太方便离开设有结界的空中庭园
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.59,0:15:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个原因是不能说的秘密吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.07,0:15:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒也不是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.92,0:15:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是…这件事不太方便多说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.83,0:15:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这与经营没有直接关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.20,0:15:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要把这件事记住就好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.49,0:15:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代理经理  怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.38,0:15:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然要继续
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.56,0:15:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要你编辑的视频还有一个  抓紧时间
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.98,0:15:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.48,0:15:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\c&H443B3A&\fn方正准雅宋_GBK\an7\fs30\pos(879,241)\frz92.109}{\fad(1000,0)}甘城光辉游乐园PV
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.48,0:15:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\c&H443B3A&\fn方正准雅宋_GBK\an7\fs20\pos(972,241)\frz91.882}{\fad(1000,0)}投稿人：甘城光辉游乐园官方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.48,0:15:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\c&H443B3A&\fn方正准雅宋_GBK\an7\fs20\pos(1010,125)\frz91.836}{\fad(1000,0)}播放次数 218
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.48,0:15:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\c&H443B3A&\fn方正准雅宋_GBK\an7\fs20\pos(1063,81)\frz91.293}{\fad(1000,0)}评论数 0
Comment: 0,0:15:58.48,0:16:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（甘城光辉游乐园PV\N投稿人：甘城光辉游乐园官方\N播放次数 218\N评论数 0）
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.23,0:16:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个视频  点击数没怎么增加啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.94,0:16:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.97,0:16:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.24,0:16:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的客人没有单纯到只是看到泳衣就会高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.48,0:16:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千斗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.65,0:16:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.55,0:16:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的入园人数有多少
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.09,0:16:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,198人  基本和历年持平
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.51,0:16:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.71,0:16:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.19,0:16:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于泳衣视频
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.74,0:16:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出了一些意料之外的状况
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.23,0:16:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.13,0:16:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.16,0:16:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就马上想对策…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.22,0:17:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hello  Everyone
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.34,0:17:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.24,0:17:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正想对可儿江同学说这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.12,0:17:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  光是存在就很惹眼的招牌吉祥物
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.76,0:17:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\b0\c&H857165&\pos(487,429)\frz26.71}干的好。同样作为服务业者赞一个。
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.72,0:17:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\b0\c&H857165&\frz27.394\pos(570,345)}那个勾拳是瞄准了打的。这个人偶不起眼却很强。
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.01,0:17:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\b0\c&H857165&\fry1\frz27.703\pos(659,362)}居然对客人使用暴力，真是个可怕的游乐园 我看错你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.22,0:17:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\frz27.584\bord0\b0\c&H857165&\pos(439,435)}这个拳头是真本事 人偶好强！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.61,0:17:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是偶发性事件
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.42,0:17:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却能像这样立下大功  这种明星素质
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.36,0:17:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的才能真是可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.41,0:17:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳衣视频的点击数有多少啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.25,0:17:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在刚过12000吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.95,0:17:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的视频呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.15,0:17:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锵锵  20万
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.12,0:17:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的那个似乎只是被我的相关链接拉了一把呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.26,0:17:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  真是遗憾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.95,0:17:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.75,0:17:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.39,0:17:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好好看看投稿人的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.27,0:17:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,AYIES
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.72,0:17:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.17,0:18:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒着念念看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.93,0:18:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西也
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.47,0:18:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.48,0:18:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你猜对了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.50,0:18:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,视频的投稿人就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.76,0:18:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特利戈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.73,0:18:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.47,0:18:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是把萨拉玛拍的视频经由代理经理和我编辑后上传的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.03,0:18:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.97,0:18:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,招牌吉祥物?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.08,0:18:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们没上传  这个视频根本就没人看得到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.32,0:18:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明星素质?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.86,0:18:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有经过我们的编辑  被当成坏人的就会是你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.70,0:18:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连偶发性事件也能用来吸引客人的这种手段
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.77,0:18:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.23,0:18:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是关键的泳衣视频没有多少人看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.22,0:18:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样能吸引客人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.03,0:18:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸引不了多少吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.03,0:18:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看了宣传视频的人之中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.09,0:18:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正能来的恐怕不到1%吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.58,0:19:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又为什么要我们穿成那个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.21,0:19:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了多招到一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.45,0:19:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此我会不择手段
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.84,0:19:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.31,0:19:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来宾在等我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.47,0:19:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代理经理  你好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.81,0:19:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的入园人数怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.16,0:19:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  增加了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.62,0:19:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正细圆_GBK\b1\bord0\c&H848AAB&\fs40\frz0.266\pos(391,204)}本日的入园人数
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.62,0:19:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正细圆_GBK\b1\bord0\c&H848AAB&\frz1.931\blur0.5\fs40\pos(398,328)}本年度入园人数
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.32,0:19:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,223人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.32,0:19:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  的确有效果了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.64,0:19:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.82,0:19:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的莫夫路先生很有干劲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.62,0:20:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.05,0:20:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们都很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.90,0:20:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不这样就麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.19,0:20:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说这是莫夫路发起的激励会
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.52,0:20:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是为什么只有我们四个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.27,0:20:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我邀请过了但是都不来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.72,0:20:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在已经不流行面对面交流啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.24,0:20:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之今天辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.25,0:20:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.62,0:20:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.81,0:20:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  莫夫路出乎意料地没人望呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.36,0:20:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是了不起的职员领导呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.24,0:20:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还是个姐控
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.65,0:20:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁说的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.34,0:20:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.98,0:21:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对拉媞珐大人过分照顾是因为莫夫路对姐姐的爱屋及乌
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.33,0:21:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我担心侄女是理所当然的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.28,0:21:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞什么  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.05,0:21:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想打架吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.46,0:21:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.71,0:21:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.99,0:21:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十铃妹妹  女孩子要文静一点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.99,0:21:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不管你喜欢什么样的女性
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.54,0:21:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十铃  你的心情好像不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.87,0:21:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那个小鬼发生什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.36,0:21:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会出现可儿江同学的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.09,0:21:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  今天经常看到你在那个小鬼旁边一副不高兴的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.48,0:21:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真令人在意呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.81,0:21:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细说来听听
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.71,0:21:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.18,0:21:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  她好像在可儿江君的家里住了一晚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.40,0:21:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活活  那也就是说…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.99,0:21:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.91,0:22:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉媞珐大人她…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.30,0:22:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,150)\fn方正宋一_GBK\bord0\blur0.5\fs34}昨天的入园人数
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.30,0:22:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,310)\fn方正宋一_GBK\bord0\blur0.5\fs34}距离50万人还有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.30,0:22:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正宋一_GBK\bord0\blur0.5\fs34\pos(640,480)}距离7月31日还有
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.73,0:23:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\move(0,0,640,515,0,233)\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\bord1\blur2}{\fs120\t(0,233,\fs60)}{\fad(0,1000)}探险!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.31,0:23:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\move(1280,0,640,515,29,279)\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\bord1\blur2}{\fs120\t(0,279,\fs60)}{\fad(0,1000)}发现!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.86,0:23:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\move(640,720,640,520,0,271)\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\bord1\blur2}{\fs180\t(0,271,\fs90)}{\fad(0,1000)}游乐设施!!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.01,0:23:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天介绍堤拉米的花园大冒险
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.07,0:23:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个有坐上去感觉糟透了的小车的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.12,0:23:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实那里似乎有幕后路线呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.92,0:23:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「似乎」是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.96,0:24:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是正式的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.78,0:24:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有传言说是提拉米偷偷带女性客人进行的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.12,0:24:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是把客人带到后台而已吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.79,0:24:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻中止
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.09,0:24:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,520)\bord1\blur3\fs60\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK}{\fad(1000,0)}第4话    秘书真没用！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.18,0:00:28.22,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Look at the sky, it's Magic Hour!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.79,0:00:43.41,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}パズルのピースはまるみたい　
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.10,0:00:48.78,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}違うカタチつなげてみる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.51,0:00:54.55,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}バラバラだと見えなかった景色が突然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.84,0:00:59.65,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}目の前に浮かんで動き出すカンジ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.12,0:01:06.99,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}新しい出会いの数だけ  change my world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:09.99,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}変わってく世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.09,0:01:12.80,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}騒然鳴り止まぬMusic
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.80,0:01:15.51,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眠っていた心響く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.69,0:01:20.34,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君と私Gradation 空を染める
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.80,0:01:28.70,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}きっと探していたのは こんな風に笑い合う時
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.43,0:01:33.78,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}輝くもの全部集めて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.01,0:01:41.61,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}終わらないMagic Hour!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:00:24.18,0:00:28.22,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}仰望天空 那是魔法的时间!
Dialogue: 1,0:00:38.79,0:00:43.41,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那一处的拼图进行不下去了
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.10,0:00:48.78,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}试着拼接起另外的部分吧
Dialogue: 1,0:00:49.51,0:00:54.55,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}分散在四处的碎片忽然之间
Dialogue: 1,0:00:54.84,0:00:59.65,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连成一片绚丽的景色
Dialogue: 1,0:01:00.12,0:01:06.99,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}每一次新的邂逅  都改变着我的世界
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:09.99,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变化万千的世界
Dialogue: 1,0:01:10.09,0:01:12.80,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}骚然不止的音乐
Dialogue: 1,0:01:12.80,0:01:15.51,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}响彻沉睡的心灵
Dialogue: 1,0:01:15.69,0:01:20.34,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你我的渐变色 将天空染色
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.80,0:01:28.70,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}探寻的一定是像这样欢笑的时刻
Dialogue: 1,0:01:29.43,0:01:33.78,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}将所有闪耀之物收集起来
Dialogue: 1,0:01:35.01,0:01:41.61,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}永不完结的魔法时间!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.04,0:22:31.39,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}言いたくて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.78,0:22:38.65,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}気持ちが燻り  心の大地熱く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.06,0:22:46.87,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自然発火的に  メラメラ炎上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.16,0:22:50.84,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}恋に焦がれて行くの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.92,0:22:56.72,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}天にも昇る  ねぇ  夢心地
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.02,0:23:05.60,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}浮ついてる台風は  誰にも止められない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.12,0:23:09.18,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Water  Wind  LandにFire
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.18,0:23:11.91,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}混ぜてスペシャルなShow
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.18,0:23:15.27,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ループループしてく心情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.27,0:23:18.30,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}まさに森羅万象でしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.30,0:23:24.22,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハッピーの雨が止まらないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.40,0:23:30.37,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}never  end  永遠のunity
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:22:27.04,0:22:31.39,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想说却说不出口
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.78,0:22:38.65,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}心情开始冒烟  心田开始变热
Dialogue: 1,0:22:39.06,0:22:46.87,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}开始自燃起来  烈火熊熊燃烧
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.16,0:22:50.84,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}让恋爱烧的更激烈一些
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.92,0:22:56.72,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}升到天空中  就好像在梦里
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.02,0:23:05.60,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}形成了一个台风  谁也无法阻止
Dialogue: 1,0:23:06.12,0:23:09.18,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}水风地火
Dialogue: 1,0:23:09.18,0:23:11.91,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}混和成特殊的Show
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.18,0:23:15.27,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}转来转去的心情
Dialogue: 1,0:23:15.27,0:23:18.30,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}正所谓的森罗万象
Dialogue: 1,0:23:18.30,0:23:24.22,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}愉快的雨停不下来
Dialogue: 1,0:23:24.40,0:23:30.37,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}never  end  永远的unity
