[Script Info]
Title:Amaburi BD 01 sc
Original Script:CASO&SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正兰亭准黑_GBK,44,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,15,1
Style: op_ja,Source Han Sans Bold,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: op_zh,思源黑体 CN Bold,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: ed_ja,Source Han Sans Bold,40,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: ed_zh,思源黑体 CN Bold,40,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,35,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.33,0:00:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很唐突
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.70,0:00:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江西也同学
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.46,0:00:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下周日  能跟我一起去游乐园吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.52,0:00:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是邀请我跟你约会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.78,0:00:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.52,0:00:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这把火枪是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.91,0:00:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了不让你逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.31,0:00:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果拒绝就开枪?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.64,0:00:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你的回答呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.66,0:00:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  突然这么说也…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.26,0:00:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江同学
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.67,0:00:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.55,0:00:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.54,0:02:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs34\bord1\blur3\3a&H80\pos(1070,715)}{\fad(500,1000)}没有客人!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.40,0:02:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也帅呆了
Dialogue: 1,0:02:32.78,0:02:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs34\an8}喂  你看那边
Dialogue: 1,0:02:34.26,0:02:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs34\an8}好像在自言自语些什么
Dialogue: 1,0:02:35.45,0:02:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs34\an8}貌似是沉醉在自恋里了
Dialogue: 1,0:02:37.39,0:02:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs34\an8}到底是多自恋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.07,0:02:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连我自己都看入迷了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.02,0:02:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此美型的我  再加上成绩拔尖
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.26,0:02:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个从未搭过话的转校生会来邀请我约会
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.78,0:02:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是不能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.08,0:02:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.51,0:02:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千斗五十铃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.92,0:02:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.96,0:03:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这是要去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.13,0:03:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘辉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.38,0:03:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘辉?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.42,0:03:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘城光辉游乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.44,0:03:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里可以坐巴士过去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.56,0:03:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.54,0:03:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  那个姐姐穿的是蓝白条纹  是基本装备哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.11,0:03:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘  一个善良的市民就该装作没看见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.93,0:03:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不去就开枪?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.61,0:03:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.74,0:03:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么偏偏是那个游乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.08,0:03:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准确说是主题乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.45,0:03:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样都好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.54,0:03:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我们两个一定要去那个微妙的游乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.29,0:03:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚转学过来的你  为什么这么想跟我约会
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.92,0:03:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确很帅  但应该也有别的原因吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.55,0:03:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这杆枪是从哪里掏出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.39,0:03:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要去那个游乐园的理由是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.73,0:03:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来你真的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.23,0:03:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘城光辉游乐园吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.90,0:03:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江同学去过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.01,0:03:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得小时候被带去过一次
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.07,0:04:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还挺壮观的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.52,0:04:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前方到站甘城光辉游乐园  甘城光辉游乐园到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.93,0:04:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 1,0:04:06.51,0:04:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs34\an8}下车时请注意脚下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.57,0:04:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一站
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.97,0:04:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那座城堡不是正门吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.02,0:04:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是爱情酒店
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.29,0:04:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.84,0:04:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是爱情酒店
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.81,0:04:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说了两遍
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.96,0:04:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常会被弄错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.87,0:04:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前这里的确是正门
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.16,0:04:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但因十年前的改建工程移走了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.44,0:04:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后留下的公交站旁建了那座城堡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.28,0:04:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真  真是复杂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.18,0:04:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不改一下公交站的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.71,0:04:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前就一直在申请
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.79,0:04:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但由于种种原因被搁置了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.53,0:04:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明在这里下错车的来宾很多
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.50,0:04:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来宾?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.44,0:04:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是指客人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.07,0:04:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分主题乐园都称呼客人为来宾
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.62,0:04:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作人员则是职员 记好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.03,0:04:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千斗五十铃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.76,0:04:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒是知道些奇怪的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.84,0:05:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进去吧  可儿江同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.32,0:05:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大周日的就这么点客人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.66,0:05:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息日的平均客流量约为2110人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.55,0:05:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道得真详细
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.14,0:05:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们先去魔法之丘吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.58,0:05:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法之丘?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.23,0:05:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是甘辉里的一块区域
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.83,0:05:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是魔法王国枫叶大陆的吉祥物们所居住的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.87,0:05:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充满了梦想的童话乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.65,0:05:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有梦想的感觉啊  千斗五十铃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.36,0:05:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是堤拉米的花园大冒险
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.76,0:05:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堤拉米是花之妖精
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.27,0:05:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们向着充满爱与喜悦的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.76,0:05:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乘着净化心灵的奇幻列车出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.65,0:05:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说完全没有心灵被净化的感觉啊  千斗五十铃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.95,0:06:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.43,0:06:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.40,0:06:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.03,0:06:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铁轨似乎错开了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.51,0:06:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很危险好不
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.56,0:06:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很危险呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.91,0:06:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢…迎…光…临…堤…拉…米
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.15,0:06:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花…园…大…冒…险…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.51,0:06:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.51,0:06:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来堤拉米会在这里朝我们挥手的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.69,0:06:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是今天也不在呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.50,0:06:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.57,0:06:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千斗五十铃  这里你来过多少次了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.77,0:06:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.95,0:06:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晕了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.93,0:06:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来去马卡隆的音乐剧场
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.16,0:06:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马卡隆是音乐妖精
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.41,0:06:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它会演奏出美妙的音乐和动听的节奏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.00,0:06:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让听众觉得充满了幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.30,0:06:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说完全没有幸福的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.81,0:06:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\frz7.689\1c&H393336&\bord0\1a&H20\pos(771,340)}本日休息
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.68,0:06:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1c&H393336&\bord0\1a&H20\fs14\pos(738,539)\frz8.101}本日休息
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.98,0:06:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没心情的时候就直接休息  艺术家都这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.27,0:06:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样也行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.95,0:07:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来莫夫路的点心屋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.10,0:07:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫夫路是点心妖精
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.96,0:07:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是甘辉的招牌吉祥物
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.48,0:07:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了它的点心  会充满梦想和希望
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.78,0:07:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.84,0:07:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临莫夫路的点心屋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.89,0:07:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这个点心屋里有很多恶作剧的老鼠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.46,0:07:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用魔法水枪让老鼠们吃点苦头吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.42,0:07:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是射击游戏吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.68,0:07:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这个打老鼠就行了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.41,0:07:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.78,0:07:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这类游戏我很擅长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.72,0:07:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情为我的反射神经感叹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.14,0:07:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  战斗开始!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.64,0:07:31.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于是战斗吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.41,0:07:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.27,0:07:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打中了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.02,0:07:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要进食物储藏库了  别大意
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.94,0:07:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  难度也太高了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.99,0:07:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集中精神
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.95,0:07:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\fn方正粗倩_GBK\c&H969B86&\pos(397,340)}老鼠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.95,0:07:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(797,346)\fn方正准雅宋_GBK\c&H4E5883&\bord0\fscx105}只中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.95,0:07:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正准雅宋_GBK\c&H4E5883&\bord0\fscx105\pos(642,476)}只
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.95,0:07:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正少儿_GBK\c&H4B45BA&\bord1.5\3a&H20\blur0.5\3c&HFFFFFF&\pos(855,444)}被杀害
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.62,0:07:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游戏鬼畜也得有点限度啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.70,0:08:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真遗憾  没杀死多少呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.25,0:08:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀掉了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.89,0:08:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说吃点苦头吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.59,0:08:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正少儿_GBK\c&H4B45BA&\bord1.5\3a&H20\blur0.5\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs60\pos(804,343)}被杀害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.70,0:08:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  老鼠杀的越多奖品越豪华
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.40,0:08:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这凶恶的设定是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.12,0:08:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种家庭向的世界里  说什么杀不杀的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.15,0:08:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微妙的有点受打击啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.75,0:08:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是莫夫路很感谢您
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.29,0:08:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在下个房间一起拍个纪念照片吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.51,0:08:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里可以跟莫夫路拍纪念照片
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.18,0:08:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没什么兴趣跟玩偶拍纪念照片
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.98,0:08:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  去见见它吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.66,0:08:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定会很开心的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.92,0:08:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有人觉得这个游乐设施开心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.20,0:08:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.63,0:08:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看那里装饰着拿到高分的来宾的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.27,0:08:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显客户群带有偏向性啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.02,0:08:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,mofu
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.33,0:08:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点心妖精  莫夫路
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.64,0:09:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这座游乐园的招牌吉祥物
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.68,0:09:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.01,0:09:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥  这股无名火是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.64,0:09:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想拍纪念照片  可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.96,0:09:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,mofu
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.07,0:09:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着  你不跟着一起拍算怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.39,0:09:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么态度
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.05,0:09:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可是客人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.62,0:09:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江同学  冷静点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.34,0:09:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我很冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.34,0:09:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会慌乱的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.91,0:09:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不愉快  走了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.53,0:09:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是有多可怜才会跟这种山寨货…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.58,0:09:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫夫路最不能忍受被人说是山寨
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.40,0:09:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有因此向客人扔相机的吉祥物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.46,0:09:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说那个有种来战的态度是怎…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.92,0:09:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.95,0:09:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.80,0:09:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.00,0:09:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被打中了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.77,0:09:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙真的开枪了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.79,0:09:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.58,0:10:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为这么无聊的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.31,0:10:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.20,0:10:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再下去会伤及性命的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.75,0:10:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别用你们的血玷污这梦想与希望的点心屋
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.26,0:10:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里什么时候有过梦想和希望了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.40,0:10:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且拿着枪乱晃的你有什么资格说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.37,0:10:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  可儿江同学
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.09,0:10:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟莫夫路交手之后感想如何
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.82,0:10:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全是单方面被揍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.51,0:10:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能好好相处吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.33,0:10:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.17,0:10:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的台词
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.13,0:10:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  可以说话的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.62,0:10:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  就这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.93,0:10:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纪念照片也拍了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.50,0:10:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去下一个地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.25,0:10:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纪念照片?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.27,0:10:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙是怎么回事  糟糕透顶的吉祥物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.78,0:10:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.79,0:10:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一只扣着帽子的暴力老鼠而已吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.32,0:10:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  真想看看里面是个什么样的混混
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.54,0:10:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面没有人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.22,0:10:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.11,0:10:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说莫夫路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.63,0:10:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面没有人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.41,0:10:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  也就是那个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.90,0:10:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了不破坏孩子们的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.84,0:10:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有演员在里面  是真正的妖精
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.61,0:10:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是约定俗成的设定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.46,0:11:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样  里面没有人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.26,0:11:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是魔法王国的居民
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.01,0:11:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法王国吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.96,0:11:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  我知道了  就当是这么回事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.72,0:11:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是屋内剧团的Erementario
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.40,0:11:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有4个精灵在舞台上表演
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.92,0:11:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精益求精的舞蹈以及让人惊呼的狂野动作是看点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.03,0:11:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是缪丝  是水之精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.81,0:11:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎您今日光临我们的Erementario
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.70,0:11:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是西尔菲  是风之精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.56,0:11:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们好好相处吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.33,0:11:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是土之精灵柯波莉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.87,0:11:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.55,0:11:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是萨拉玛  火之精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.75,0:11:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.30,0:11:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常有精神呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.74,0:11:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  鼓起干劲开始咯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.81,0:11:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.07,0:11:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.69,0:11:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去下一个地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.17,0:11:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳过山车
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.66,0:12:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体验颤栗与兴奋风驰电掣的子弹列车
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.87,0:12:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕了?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.86,0:12:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.27,0:12:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那去乘坐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.12,0:12:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.10,0:12:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.10,0:12:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  去下一个地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.33,0:12:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光辉市场
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.13,0:12:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堆满了甘辉最新的周边
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.27,0:12:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仿佛回到了昭和时代呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.73,0:12:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淘气广场
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.16,0:12:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让孩子们尽情欢笑的自由空间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.95,0:12:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪来的欢笑
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.63,0:12:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由落体
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.83,0:12:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让小孩子也能愉快地玩耍  控制了下降速度
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.87,0:12:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控制过头了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.44,0:12:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咖啡杯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.73,0:12:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘辉的卖点是速度和颤栗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.03,0:12:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算哪门子的颤栗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.96,0:12:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.15,0:12:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你生气了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.32,0:12:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然  这些个游乐设施真够微妙的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.57,0:12:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,服务差劲  设备陈旧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.64,0:13:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隔壁的爱情旅馆都比这里像样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.26,0:13:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说这个主题乐园太小看娱乐这个要素了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.56,0:13:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定认为无非是骗骗小孩子的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.26,0:13:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而  欺骗小孩是非常严重的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.83,0:13:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多就行的想法是成不了大事的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.55,0:13:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要怀着强烈的意志以及信念才行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.78,0:13:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这些东西完全不存在于这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.61,0:13:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要向别人展现出你的梦想的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.81,0:13:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先自己要去相信那个梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.57,0:13:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.56,0:13:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要向别人展现出你的梦想的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.52,0:13:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先自己要去相信那个梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.63,0:13:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是说到了痛处
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.64,0:13:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不认为一介高中生能说出这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.52,0:13:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现学现卖  从书里看来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.59,0:13:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不高兴是因为受到个莫名其妙的女人威胁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.50,0:13:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被带去一个游乐园毫无目的地闲逛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.55,0:14:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来你也知道这么做不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.58,0:14:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而不满的却是另外的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.48,0:14:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是在生这个主题乐园的气啊  真不可思议
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.99,0:14:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江西也  甘城高校2年级4班  16岁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.16,0:14:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.78,0:14:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与姑姑住在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.75,0:14:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然间怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.85,0:14:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眉清目秀  成绩优秀  运动神经拔群
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.90,0:14:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.73,0:14:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多才多艺  基本没有做不好的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.49,0:14:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过却是个自恋狂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.68,0:14:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级喜欢自己  不顾及周围怎么看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.95,0:14:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.63,0:14:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以没有朋友也没有女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.75,0:14:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.57,0:14:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午休时没人陪着一起吃饭  所以一直是在吃独食
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.99,0:14:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么连这种事都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.12,0:14:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用心调查的结果
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.16,0:14:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么回事  为什么要调查我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.89,0:14:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿玉诚也
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.64,0:14:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经有这么一个天才童星
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.24,0:14:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一个大人理想中的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.84,0:15:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在5年前  儿玉诚也忽然就隐退了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.66,0:15:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在成了高中生的他看见这个游乐园后
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.71,0:15:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会作何感想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.80,0:15:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.50,0:15:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道这些特意把我带过来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.04,0:15:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.64,0:15:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的目的是什么我不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.80,0:15:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那个叫儿玉诚也的人早死了  已经消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.84,0:15:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你妄想能利用那个白痴童星的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.11,0:15:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直是白费力气
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.24,0:15:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去了  想用那杆枪威胁我的话就威胁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.16,0:15:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.93,0:15:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去之前尝尝这个  冷掉就太浪费了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.27,0:15:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可乐饼就免了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.06,0:15:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就尝尝看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.94,0:15:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面饼轻薄 不失酥脆感
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.16,0:15:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面多汁松软
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.13,0:16:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精制的肉馅及土豆泥搭配出了绝妙的口感
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.37,0:16:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.62,0:16:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.87,0:16:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在这里制作的  别的地方吃不到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.59,0:16:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是你?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.16,0:16:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是别人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.38,0:16:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去前不去见一面?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.46,0:16:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H0F1819&\fn方正准雅宋_GBK\bord0\pos(640,585)\shad0.2\bord0.1\blur0.5\4c&HFFFFFF&}非相关人员  禁止入内
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.42,0:16:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然是这里的内部人员啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.89,0:16:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没说过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.03,0:16:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  虽然你讲话的口气就是内部人员
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.63,0:16:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.86,0:16:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枫叶城的屋顶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.73,0:16:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这座游乐园的经理在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.90,0:16:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经理?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.78,0:16:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江同学  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.98,0:17:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.92,0:17:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那请你去她那边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.97,0:17:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.32,0:17:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问您就是可儿江西也大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.96,0:17:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.26,0:17:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是拉媞珐·芙尔兰札
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.10,0:17:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个主题乐园的经理
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.51,0:17:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经理?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.67,0:17:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.77,0:17:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天您能特意来到此地  真是非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.25,0:17:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.73,0:17:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那可乐饼是你做的?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.71,0:17:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  每天都有在做
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.35,0:17:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让各位来宾能品尝到的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.53,0:17:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我还是不太明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.37,0:17:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我有什么事  你是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.29,0:17:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您已经参观过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.30,0:17:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这座甘城光辉游乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.12,0:18:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  已经看够了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.46,0:18:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您感觉怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.23,0:18:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.01,0:18:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.48,0:18:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想必您相当不满吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.60,0:18:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.86,0:18:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一个请求
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.95,0:18:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望您能重振这个濒临灭亡的游乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.75,0:18:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.03,0:18:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请您成为这个甘城光辉游乐园的经理
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.18,0:18:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我成为这里的经理?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.92,0:18:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.05,0:18:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是您  一定能拯救这个游乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.16,0:18:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是下达给我们的神谕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.40,0:18:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神谕?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.34,0:18:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是神明的旨意
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.84,0:18:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是魔法王国枫叶大陆的居民
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.77,0:18:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枫叶大陆?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.74,0:18:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.89,0:18:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是这个地上世界的人  而是真正来自魔法王国的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.41,0:19:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这座甘城光辉游乐园里的大部分职员都是魔法王国枫叶大陆的居民
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.92,0:19:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.73,0:19:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.61,0:19:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果在接下来的3个月内不能吸引到25万名客人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.71,0:19:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这座游乐园就会被关闭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.22,0:19:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果变成那样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.49,0:19:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们枫叶大陆的居民就会失去容身之所
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.65,0:19:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生存之力也会消失殆尽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.04,0:19:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  就算你突然说什么真正的魔法王国…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.14,0:19:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您无法相信吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.23,0:19:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.64,0:19:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  接下来我会赋予您魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.24,0:19:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.06,0:19:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.79,0:19:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江大人  请不要动
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.32,0:20:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江大人  可儿江大人  您没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.35,0:20:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十铃  快过来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.86,0:20:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点将可儿江大人送进屋里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.25,0:20:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江大人  可儿江大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.01,0:20:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的房间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.93,0:20:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去洗个脸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.79,0:20:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  蓝珠姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.68,0:21:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在的吧  快出来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.17,0:21:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.97,0:21:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.58,0:21:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.40,0:21:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么呀  大清早的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.76,0:21:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  为什么那个女人在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.81,0:21:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说五十铃妹妹?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.26,0:21:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚她把摔晕过去的你给背回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.94,0:21:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一班电车已经错过了  所以就让她住下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.89,0:21:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过西也居然会和女孩子约会  也变成熟了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.00,0:21:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前还总把女孩子当成敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.10,0:21:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是令人欣慰呢  作为监护人来说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.92,0:21:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蓝珠姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.92,0:21:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才是不是用奇怪的语气说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.94,0:21:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说我变成熟了什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.14,0:21:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  不懂你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.38,0:21:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你刚才闭着嘴说了许多话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.79,0:21:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.27,0:21:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我大概是睡迷糊了  酒也还没醒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.33,0:21:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  再睡一觉  再睡一觉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.81,0:21:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你就乖乖去上学吧  再见
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.80,0:21:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江同学
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.53,0:21:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能使用魔法了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.71,0:21:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.73,0:22:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下你该相信了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.34,0:22:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,150)\fn方正宋一_GBK\bord0\blur0.5\fs34}昨天的入园人数
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.34,0:22:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,310)\fn方正宋一_GBK\bord0\blur0.5\fs34}距离50万人还有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.34,0:22:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正宋一_GBK\bord0\blur0.5\fs34\pos(640,480)}距离7月31日还有
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.48,0:23:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\move(0,0,640,515,0,233)\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\bord1\blur1}{\fs120\t(0,233,\fs60)}{\fad(0,1000)}探险!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.06,0:23:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\move(1280,0,640,515,29,279)\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\bord1\blur1}{\fs120\t(0,279,\fs60)}{\fad(0,1000)}发现!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.61,0:23:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\move(640,720,640,520,0,271)\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\bord1\blur1}{\fs180\t(0,271,\fs90)}{\fad(0,1000)}游乐设施!!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.22,0:23:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个版块将为大家介绍甘辉的一些有趣的游乐设施
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.12,0:23:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,语气更开心一点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.51,0:23:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一回就介绍这里  莫夫路的点心屋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.57,0:23:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实可以设定难度
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.29,0:24:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简单  普通  困难
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.13,0:24:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及最残酷的疯狂
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.24,0:24:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说太过激烈而导致有的来宾精神失常
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.14,0:24:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.25,0:24:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带一提  这次可儿江同学玩的是简单
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.39,0:24:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.13,0:24:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,520)\bord1\blur2\fs60\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK}{\fad(1000,0)}第2话  没有时间 !
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.26,0:00:59.30,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Look at the sky, it's Magic Hour!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.87,0:01:14.49,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}パズルのピースはまるみたい　
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.18,0:01:19.86,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}違うカタチつなげてみる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.59,0:01:25.63,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}バラバラだと見えなかった景色が突然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.92,0:01:30.73,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}目の前に浮かんで動き出すカンジ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.20,0:01:38.07,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}新しい出会いの数だけ  change my world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.07,0:01:41.07,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}変わってく世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.17,0:01:43.88,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}騒然鳴り止まぬMusic
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.88,0:01:46.59,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眠っていた心響く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.77,0:01:51.42,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君と私Gradation 空を染める
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.88,0:01:59.78,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}きっと探していたのは こんな風に笑い合う時
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.51,0:02:04.86,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}輝くもの全部集めて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.09,0:02:12.69,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}終わらないMagic Hour!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.26,0:00:59.30,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}仰望天空 那是魔法的时间!
Dialogue: 1,0:01:09.87,0:01:14.49,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那一处的拼图进行不下去了
Dialogue: 1,0:01:15.18,0:01:19.86,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}试着拼接起另外的部分吧
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.59,0:01:25.63,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}分散在四处的碎片忽然之间
Dialogue: 1,0:01:25.92,0:01:30.73,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连成一片绚丽的景色
Dialogue: 1,0:01:31.20,0:01:38.07,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}每一次新的邂逅  都改变着我的世界
Dialogue: 1,0:01:38.07,0:01:41.07,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变化万千的世界
Dialogue: 1,0:01:41.17,0:01:43.88,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}骚然不止的音乐
Dialogue: 1,0:01:43.88,0:01:46.59,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}响彻沉睡的心灵
Dialogue: 1,0:01:46.77,0:01:51.42,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你我的渐变色 将天空染色
Dialogue: 1,0:01:51.88,0:01:59.78,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}探寻的一定是像这样欢笑的时刻
Dialogue: 1,0:02:00.51,0:02:04.86,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}将所有闪耀之物收集起来
Dialogue: 1,0:02:06.09,0:02:12.69,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}永不完结的魔法时间!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.04,0:22:31.39,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}言いたくて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.78,0:22:38.65,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}気持ちが燻り  心の大地熱く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.06,0:22:46.87,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自然発火的に  メラメラ炎上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.16,0:22:50.84,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}恋に焦がれて行くの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.92,0:22:56.72,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}天にも昇る  ねぇ  夢心地
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.02,0:23:05.60,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}浮ついてる台風は  誰にも止められない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.12,0:23:09.18,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Water  Wind  LandにFire
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.18,0:23:11.91,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}混ぜてスペシャルなShow
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.18,0:23:15.27,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ループループしてく心情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.27,0:23:18.30,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}まさに森羅万象でしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.30,0:23:24.22,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハッピーの雨が止まらないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.40,0:23:30.37,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}never  end  永遠のunity
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:22:27.04,0:22:31.39,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想说却说不出口
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.78,0:22:38.65,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}心情开始冒烟  心田开始变热
Dialogue: 1,0:22:39.06,0:22:46.87,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}开始自燃起来  烈火熊熊燃烧
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.16,0:22:50.84,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}让恋爱烧的更激烈一些
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.92,0:22:56.72,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}升到天空中  就好像在梦里
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.02,0:23:05.60,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}形成了一个台风  谁也无法阻止
Dialogue: 1,0:23:06.12,0:23:09.18,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}水风地火
Dialogue: 1,0:23:09.18,0:23:11.91,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}混和成特殊的Show
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.18,0:23:15.27,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}转来转去的心情
Dialogue: 1,0:23:15.27,0:23:18.30,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}正所谓的森罗万象
Dialogue: 1,0:23:18.30,0:23:24.22,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}愉快的雨停不下来
Dialogue: 1,0:23:24.40,0:23:30.37,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}never  end  永远的unity
