[Script Info]
Title:Amaburi BD 04 sc
Original Script:CASO&SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正兰亭准黑_GBK,44,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,15,1
Style: op_ja,Source Han Sans Bold,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: op_zh,思源黑体 CN Bold,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: ed_ja,Source Han Sans Bold,40,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: ed_zh,思源黑体 CN Bold,40,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.5,0,2,10,10,35,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.08,0:00:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  只是没站稳晕倒了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.20,0:00:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  听说你倒下就马上过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.84,0:00:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  大家太夸张了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.80,0:00:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  谢谢你们为我担心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.22,0:00:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公主殿下的身体不是很好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.85,0:00:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是因为我让她穿泳衣的缘故吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.33,0:00:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概不是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.23,0:00:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.77,0:00:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔会有这样的事情发生  记好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.67,0:02:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs34\bord1\blur3\3a&H80\pos(1055,715)}{\fad(500,1000)}秘书真没用！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.94,0:02:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好很好  变得有模有样了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.32,0:02:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  不过还是有些人没什么干劲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.42,0:02:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客流量怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.74,0:02:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,增加了  得益于30日元的活动
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.65,0:02:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.05,0:02:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来远足咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.67,0:02:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大闹一场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.67,0:02:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇到远足客人的话  也有这样的苦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.82,0:03:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么还这么悠闲  去帮忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.92,0:03:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.33,0:03:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.74,0:03:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待客人还是做得到的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.51,0:03:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成做不到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.48,0:03:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然能做到  你看好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.60,0:03:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到梦之国度
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.21,0:03:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么需要我做的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.42,0:03:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是女的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.14,0:03:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把水和吃的交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.15,0:03:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓紧点  今天必须处理的事情还有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.75,0:03:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不正抓紧着的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.07,0:03:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先去营业部处理新的导游展板
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.83,0:03:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  正往那边赶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.52,0:03:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.96,0:03:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉让你们来跑一趟
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.04,0:03:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于新的导游展板
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.56,0:03:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经设计好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.22,0:03:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  有五种方案
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.62,0:03:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都否决
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.92,0:04:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否…否决吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.59,0:04:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这已经花了一周的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.47,0:04:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.54,0:04:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种展板呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.73,0:04:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要这样  这样  然后这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.71,0:04:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看变好看了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.97,0:04:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害  转眼就不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.56,0:04:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鄙人特利戈  不禁身体前倾了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.96,0:04:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细节方面就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.82,0:04:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了  千斗  去下个地方  抓紧点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.08,0:04:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来得太晚啦  代理经理
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.64,0:04:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  然后储备呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.64,0:04:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这些了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.20,0:04:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照这样下去  下周就不够用了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.48,0:04:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前的供货商供应不上来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.14,0:04:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么去找新的供货商
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.64,0:04:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么也要在下周之前…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.96,0:04:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前段时间受您照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.63,0:04:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是甘城光辉游乐园的可儿江
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.20,0:04:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是需要您的帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.08,0:04:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在下单  就麻烦您了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.08,0:04:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下单就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.80,0:04:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  帮大忙了…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.49,0:04:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了  千斗  抓紧点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.65,0:04:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代理经理  关于预算书
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.78,0:04:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了不必要的支出
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.82,0:05:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预算书?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.16,0:05:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,服饰的修缮预算书
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.25,0:05:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得是这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.24,0:05:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是这个  这个和这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.75,0:05:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,346)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.34,0:05:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,322)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.38,0:05:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,280)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.42,0:05:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,235)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.46,0:05:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,191)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.50,0:05:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,151)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.54,0:05:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,118)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.59,0:05:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,95)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.63,0:05:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,461)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.96,0:05:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,444)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.00,0:05:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,397)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.05,0:05:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,327)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.09,0:05:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,248)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.13,0:05:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,172)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.17,0:05:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,111)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.21,0:05:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,71)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.25,0:05:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\bord0\fs30\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,57)}Cosplay服装\N{\fscy330}\h{\fscy100}\N角色佩戴饰物\N{\fscy280}\h{\fscy100}\N制服C\N{\fscy240}\h{\fscy100}\N外借用 制服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.42,0:05:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,682)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.46,0:05:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,638)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.50,0:05:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,598)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.54,0:05:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,565)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.59,0:05:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,542)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.63,0:05:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,532)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.96,0:05:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,516)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.00,0:05:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,469)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.05,0:05:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,400)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.09,0:05:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,321)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.13,0:05:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,245)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.17,0:05:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,183)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.21,0:05:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,143)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.25,0:05:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\fs24\fn方正书宋_GBK\fscx90\c&H403933&\pos(188,130)}工作用 连衣裤\N{\fscy310}\h{\fscy100}\N职员特殊夹克\N{\fscy350}\h{\fscy100}\N职员雨衣\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N工作用长靴\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N职员用鞋\N{\fscy380}\h{\fscy100}\N制服B
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.40,0:05:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.71,0:05:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是必要的支出
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.03,0:05:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照这样进行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.12,0:05:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.36,0:05:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.69,0:05:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的泵噪音相当大
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.15,0:05:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么去咨询制造商…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.44,0:05:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有预算  停用一台
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.78,0:05:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后把部件挪用到其他两台上去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.54,0:05:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.81,0:05:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话  要是有个万一…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.31,0:05:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那时候再说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.88,0:05:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解了  老大
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.54,0:05:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.86,0:05:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商品的存放位置不够
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.47,0:05:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里空着呢  全部搬过去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.23,0:05:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警备用的器材损坏
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.32,0:05:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  修好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.29,0:05:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食堂的韭菜炒肝不好吃…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.54,0:05:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.40,0:05:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超人气偶像被发现在外过夜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.14,0:05:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种杂志赶紧扔了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.05,0:06:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来还有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.21,0:06:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些文件的处理
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.89,0:06:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及协商对娱乐设施的翻新
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.80,0:06:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,协商?跟谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.04,0:06:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫夫路  马卡隆  堤拉米三人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.26,0:06:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.42,0:06:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.39,0:06:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.40,0:06:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天已经累了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.14,0:06:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有力气去跟那三个笨蛋搅合了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.41,0:06:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处理文件更省力一些
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.26,0:06:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.84,0:06:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  千斗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.25,0:06:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处理的尽量圆滑一些  圆滑一些哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.18,0:06:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用你多说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.77,0:06:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  千斗你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.60,0:06:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是奇怪的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.85,0:06:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.93,0:06:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门开着呢  进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.91,0:06:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.29,0:06:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.78,0:06:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点麻烦的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.00,0:07:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以想让可儿江先生您听一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.65,0:07:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在正忙着处理文件呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.49,0:07:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能给千斗说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.75,0:07:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边不听所以才只能跟你说的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.61,0:07:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  没有  不是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.73,0:07:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想直接跟可儿江先生您商量下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.00,0:07:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说到底什么事儿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.50,0:07:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  赶紧说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.99,0:07:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么说明呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.30,0:07:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他直接看看比较好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.25,0:07:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这样比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.83,0:07:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能稍微占用点您的时间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.35,0:07:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看这个  破破烂烂的了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.84,0:07:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能给点购置新器材的预算啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.25,0:07:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否决  你也知道现在资金不足吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.73,0:07:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  这样的水枪会让客人失望的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.83,0:07:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的任务就是解决这个事情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.58,0:07:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请全力迎击客人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.90,0:07:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迎击?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.16,0:07:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种子弹倒是有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.39,0:08:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看这个  破破烂烂的了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.55,0:08:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买个新的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.26,0:08:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否决
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.28,0:08:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用别的器材来代替吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.15,0:08:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  这样下去客人们都会逃走的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.09,0:08:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人要是逃了  就全力追击
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.07,0:08:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追击…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.22,0:08:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请拿出全力认真处理  知道了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.97,0:08:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.45,0:08:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事说事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.01,0:08:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄错了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.55,0:08:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.73,0:08:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会说话的花  破破烂烂的了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.64,0:08:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.31,0:08:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否决
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.35,0:08:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自行处理
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.29,0:08:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.83,0:08:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自行处理
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.14,0:08:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.92,0:08:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多事都不好拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.16,0:08:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们商量什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.15,0:08:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰巧遇到而已  碰巧啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.25,0:08:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是偶然碰到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.47,0:09:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么不满可以跟我说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.35,0:09:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过请不要去烦他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.76,0:09:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  不是这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.79,0:09:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千斗  过来下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.76,0:09:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说过要处理的圆滑一些
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.77,0:09:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应你的要求  我圆滑的处理了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.20,0:09:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里圆滑了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.35,0:09:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用枪威胁  让对方服从
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.48,0:09:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样不是跟请我过来的时候一样了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.27,0:09:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要去威胁他们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.78,0:09:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽量找到两全的办法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.27,0:09:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用高压让他们服从绝对不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.17,0:09:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也是采用的高压政策吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.43,0:09:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.44,0:09:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我让他们认同了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.04,0:09:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该不会就这样做了一年的代理经理吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.08,0:09:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.68,0:09:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.11,0:09:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你现在是我的秘书
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.04,0:09:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像这样扯我的后腿  我可受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.66,0:09:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说我扯你后腿?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.26,0:09:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是照那样下去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.14,0:10:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你说  我还能怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.31,0:10:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千斗…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.49,0:10:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  千斗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.56,0:10:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咋回事啊  真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.64,0:10:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.38,0:10:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉媞法  身体怎么样…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.35,0:10:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是可儿江大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.38,0:10:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.55,0:10:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.59,0:11:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我还以为是五十铃小姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.91,0:11:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好些了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.47,0:11:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.38,0:11:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.24,0:11:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以刚想去外面吹吹风呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.82,0:11:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  这样说不定也挺好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.84,0:11:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江大人  能陪我一会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.39,0:11:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很旧  但是这个摩天轮很棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.12,0:11:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.08,0:11:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前就想请你来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.51,0:11:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉像是约会一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.78,0:11:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.38,0:11:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  能看见正门了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.76,0:11:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边是世外桃源呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.83,0:11:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.77,0:11:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那前面是野性之谷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.32,0:11:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.25,0:11:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.53,0:11:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.81,0:11:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  这景色绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.06,0:11:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成你恐高…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.86,0:11:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.01,0:11:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我这样的人会恐高吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.23,0:12:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江大人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.01,0:12:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.90,0:12:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.30,0:12:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐高
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.14,0:12:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.80,0:12:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静下心来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.60,0:12:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.95,0:12:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早知道就不邀请您来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.34,0:12:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的虚荣和倔强造成的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.33,0:12:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.03,0:12:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.80,0:12:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  这件事请保密
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.59,0:12:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.98,0:12:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  还是告诉五十铃小姐比较好…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.11,0:12:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.45,0:12:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对要保密
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.83,0:12:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.24,0:12:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.38,0:12:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  有点好笑
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.96,0:13:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  拉媞法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.28,0:13:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.25,0:13:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们曾经见过面吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.80,0:13:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和可儿江大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.81,0:13:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.35,0:13:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我记不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.70,0:13:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真和平啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.36,0:13:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防万一要监视一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.61,0:13:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结界外是很危险的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.43,0:13:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是在意她和可儿江二人独处吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.64,0:13:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.23,0:14:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大的雨呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.46,0:14:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么大的雨很少见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.55,0:14:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏这场雨  可以悠闲一阵了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.61,0:14:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得倒轻松  客人是零啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.49,0:14:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缪丝妹妹  你是水精灵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.74,0:14:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想办法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.02,0:14:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的  水杂技我倒是很在行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.40,0:14:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次又怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.39,0:14:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.99,0:14:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.40,0:14:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生锈了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.57,0:14:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排水设备…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.65,0:14:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这场大雨让这堆破烂罢工了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.51,0:14:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去地下设施会被水淹没的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.80,0:14:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.08,0:14:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重大打击
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.57,0:14:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会一个月不能营业的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.64,0:14:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在这种时候故障
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.26,0:14:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大将  昨天跟你说过了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.89,0:14:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说停掉一台
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.52,0:14:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话  要是有个万一…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.25,0:14:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此对剩下两台增加了负担吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.71,0:14:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.86,0:14:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  没时间磨蹭了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.75,0:15:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  对了…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.08,0:15:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先转移商品…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.70,0:15:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  比起这个职员的安全
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.75,0:15:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  如果不在水淹之前阻止的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.36,0:15:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新营业之前一切就都完了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.55,0:15:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,设立对策总部
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.58,0:15:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千斗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.31,0:15:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来会议室
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.57,0:15:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.84,0:15:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将各处的消防水泵配备到10个重要场所
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.78,0:15:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是音乐剧场班
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.53,0:15:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消防水泵回收完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.49,0:15:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各排水班  在水泵到达之前用水桶接力排水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.44,0:15:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时用沙袋防止水淹扩大
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.98,0:15:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是设备班
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.35,0:15:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第4通道的水淹已经阻止住了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.03,0:15:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续去第5通道的西边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.38,0:15:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.42,0:15:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水泵配备完成
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.98,0:15:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.50,0:15:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各班  开始排水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.06,0:15:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.16,0:15:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请开始排水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.55,0:15:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始排水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.40,0:15:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始排水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.71,0:15:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.67,0:16:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是元素之屋班
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.89,0:16:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直在用水桶接力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.47,0:16:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给这边也送点水泵来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.15,0:16:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水泵全用在受灾严重的地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.37,0:16:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让警备部过去支援
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.11,0:16:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大黑  你过去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.87,0:16:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.27,0:16:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再撑20分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.27,0:16:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法控制  我无法控制
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.78,0:16:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我死守
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.92,0:16:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs34}临阵逃跑是要枪毙的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.60,0:16:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿修  换我来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.06,0:16:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去准备一下大家吃饭和休息的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.58,0:16:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.90,0:16:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总部  这里是设备班
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.17,0:16:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排水设备修好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.14,0:16:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重复  排水设备修好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.93,0:17:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总部  明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.01,0:17:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.20,0:17:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  这是你的功劳
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.52,0:17:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好  原代理经理
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.32,0:17:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我回去工作了  再见
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.23,0:17:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里似乎也没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.06,0:17:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.56,0:17:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是最后一处吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.97,0:17:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.97,0:17:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可儿江君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.10,0:17:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.52,0:17:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是对你不满
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.38,0:17:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.47,0:17:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.01,0:17:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你来这里之前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.74,0:17:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是这座游乐园的代理经理
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.07,0:17:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是一个只会用高压态度命令职员的军人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.60,0:17:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军人?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.25,0:17:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是近卫兵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.51,0:17:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家是武门世家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.63,0:17:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也毫无疑问地成为了军人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.59,0:18:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这里是因为上面命令我来重建游乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.61,0:18:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还真是轻率地命令啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.89,0:18:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.76,0:18:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我也知道这个任务不适合我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.19,0:18:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.91,0:18:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能辜负期待
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.23,0:18:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能竭尽全力不辱家名
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.96,0:18:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果没能做到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.51,0:18:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精英的第一次挫折吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.02,0:18:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挫折?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.51,0:18:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.63,0:18:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去在意家庭问题  逃走不就好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.64,0:18:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千斗?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.10,0:18:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  我从没往这方面想过
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.33,0:18:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.49,0:18:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  我失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.95,0:18:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道该如何面对这个事实
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.31,0:18:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,职员们也都讨厌我了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.04,0:19:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挫折的话  我也不输给你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.11,0:19:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有恐高症
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.66,0:19:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我还是童星的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.80,0:19:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该…怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.80,0:19:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然害怕起高处了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.48,0:19:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你差不多
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.83,0:19:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是害怕让父母失望  害怕失去人气
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.79,0:19:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到现在还不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.33,0:19:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然那不是直接原因
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.29,0:19:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候我辞掉了艺人的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.64,0:19:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被人斥责  令人失望
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.76,0:19:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给各处都添了麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.46,0:19:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直糟透了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.84,0:19:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.02,0:19:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.87,0:19:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.10,0:20:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本大爷和你那小小的挫折
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.74,0:20:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是常有的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.94,0:20:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然会为那种事情烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.09,0:20:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个人真无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.72,0:20:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.54,0:20:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太无聊了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.79,0:20:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  服了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.47,0:20:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.10,0:20:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定真是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.09,0:20:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白就好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.57,0:20:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.01,0:20:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你会对我说这些
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.76,0:20:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.37,0:20:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.48,0:20:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.62,0:20:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.84,0:20:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  五十铃小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.69,0:20:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害  五十铃妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.08,0:20:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.00,0:20:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很累  总之谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.78,0:21:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你说被他们讨厌了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.31,0:21:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在还这么想吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.95,0:21:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.42,0:21:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你昨天好像和公主殿下一起坐摩天轮了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.21,0:21:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你知道了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.20,0:21:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听马卡隆说的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.55,0:21:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  恐高症没关系了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.46,0:21:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要你管
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.69,0:21:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克服了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.16,0:21:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样都无所谓吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.70,0:21:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.26,0:21:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饶了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.58,0:21:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,150)\fn方正宋一_GBK\bord0\blur0.5\fs34}昨天的入园人数
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.58,0:21:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,310)\fn方正宋一_GBK\bord0\blur0.5\fs34}距离50万人还有
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.58,0:21:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正宋一_GBK\bord0\blur0.5\fs34\pos(640,480)}距离7月31日还有
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.32,0:23:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\move(0,0,640,515,0,233)\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\bord1\blur2}{\fs120\t(0,233,\fs60)}{\fad(0,1000)}探险!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.90,0:23:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\move(1280,0,640,515,29,279)\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\bord1\blur2}{\fs120\t(0,279,\fs60)}{\fad(0,1000)}发现!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.45,0:23:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\move(640,720,640,520,0,271)\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\bord1\blur2}{\fs180\t(0,271,\fs90)}{\fad(0,1000)}游乐设施!!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.65,0:23:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是元素之屋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.11,0:23:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四精灵的舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.76,0:23:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能用魔法进行更华丽的表演吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.01,0:23:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.16,0:23:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在室内  所以不能用大火
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.36,0:23:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用水的话事后清扫会很麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.41,0:24:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不能在地板上打洞
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.53,0:24:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹吹风总可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.45,0:24:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个已经在做了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.94,0:24:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从缝隙间吹进来的风
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.55,0:24:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让冬天的观众们都冻坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.43,0:24:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我修好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.13,0:24:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,520)\bord1\blur3\fs60\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK}{\fad(1000,0)}第5话    钱不够用！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.18,0:00:56.22,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Look at the sky, it's Magic Hour!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.79,0:01:11.41,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}パズルのピースはまるみたい　
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.10,0:01:16.78,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}違うカタチつなげてみる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.51,0:01:22.55,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}バラバラだと見えなかった景色が突然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.84,0:01:27.65,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}目の前に浮かんで動き出すカンジ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.12,0:01:35.01,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}新しい出会いの数だけ  change my world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.01,0:01:37.99,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}変わってく世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.09,0:01:40.80,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}騒然鳴り止まぬMusic
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.80,0:01:43.51,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眠っていた心響く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.69,0:01:48.34,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君と私Gradation 空を染める
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.80,0:01:56.70,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}きっと探していたのは こんな風に笑い合う時
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.43,0:02:01.78,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}輝くもの全部集めて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.01,0:02:09.61,op_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}終わらないMagic Hour!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:00:52.18,0:00:56.22,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}仰望天空 那是魔法的时间!
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.79,0:01:11.41,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那一处的拼图进行不下去了
Dialogue: 1,0:01:12.10,0:01:16.78,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}试着拼接起另外的部分吧
Dialogue: 1,0:01:17.51,0:01:22.55,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}分散在四处的碎片忽然之间
Dialogue: 1,0:01:22.84,0:01:27.65,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连成一片绚丽的景色
Dialogue: 1,0:01:28.12,0:01:35.01,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}每一次新的邂逅  都改变着我的世界
Dialogue: 1,0:01:35.01,0:01:37.99,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变化万千的世界
Dialogue: 1,0:01:38.09,0:01:40.80,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}骚然不止的音乐
Dialogue: 1,0:01:40.80,0:01:43.51,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}响彻沉睡的心灵
Dialogue: 1,0:01:43.69,0:01:48.34,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你我的渐变色 将天空染色
Dialogue: 1,0:01:48.80,0:01:56.70,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}探寻的一定是像这样欢笑的时刻
Dialogue: 1,0:01:57.43,0:02:01.78,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}将所有闪耀之物收集起来
Dialogue: 1,0:02:03.01,0:02:09.61,op_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}永不完结的魔法时间!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.04,0:22:31.39,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}言いたくて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.78,0:22:38.65,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}気持ちが燻り  心の大地熱く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.06,0:22:46.87,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}自然発火的に  メラメラ炎上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.16,0:22:50.84,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}恋に焦がれて行くの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.92,0:22:56.72,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}天にも昇る  ねぇ  夢心地
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.02,0:23:05.60,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}浮ついてる台風は  誰にも止められない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.12,0:23:09.18,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Water  Wind  LandにFire
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.18,0:23:11.91,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}混ぜてスペシャルなShow
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.18,0:23:15.27,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ループループしてく心情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.27,0:23:18.30,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}まさに森羅万象でしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.30,0:23:24.22,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハッピーの雨が止まらないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.40,0:23:30.37,ed_ja,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}never  end  永遠のunity
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:22:27.04,0:22:31.39,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想说却说不出口
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.78,0:22:38.65,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}心情开始冒烟  心田开始变热
Dialogue: 1,0:22:39.06,0:22:46.87,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}开始自燃起来  烈火熊熊燃烧
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.16,0:22:50.84,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}让恋爱烧的更激烈一些
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.92,0:22:56.72,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}升到天空中  就好像在梦里
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.02,0:23:05.60,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}形成了一个台风  谁也无法阻止
Dialogue: 1,0:23:06.12,0:23:09.18,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}水风地火
Dialogue: 1,0:23:09.18,0:23:11.91,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}混和成特殊的Show
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.18,0:23:15.27,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}转来转去的心情
Dialogue: 1,0:23:15.27,0:23:18.30,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}正所谓的森罗万象
Dialogue: 1,0:23:18.30,0:23:24.22,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}愉快的雨停不下来
Dialogue: 1,0:23:24.40,0:23:30.37,ed_zh,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}never  end  永远的unity
