[Script Info]
Title: DANGANRONPA3 To Side Future 04 sc
Original Script: SumiSora&CASO
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
PlayResX: 1280
PlayResY: 720
Timer: 100.0000
YCbCr Matrix: TV.709

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正正粗黑_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H00430880,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,1.2,2,20,20,12,1
Style: DefaultM,方正正粗黑_GBK,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H00430880,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,20,20,96,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00E7822A,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,2,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Tittle,华文中宋,70,&H00CCCCCC,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H003A3A3A,-1,0,0,0,100,135,1,0,1,0,9,1,10,10,10,1
Style: TittleN,方正小标宋,70,&H00CCCCCC,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H003A3A3A,-1,0,0,0,100,110,1,0,1,0,9,1,10,10,10,1
Style: GAME,方正像素12,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00E7822A,&H0027250C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,3,2,10,10,10,1
Style: GAME2,方正像素12,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00E7822A,&H0027250C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TIPS,方正尚酷简体,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H000000B9,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,115,0,0,1,2.5,0,8,20,20,30,1
Style: Default8bit,方正像素12,39,&H00FFFFFF,&H000019FF,&H00430880,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,93,0,0,1,2.5,1.2,2,20,20,17,1
Style: OPJP,MBitmapSquareHK-Light,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,10,10,22,1
Style: OPCN,方正像素12,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,22,1
Style: EDJP,A-OTF Folk Pro B,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00941FB2,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,22,128
Style: EDCN,方正剑体简体,43,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00941FB2,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,22,1
Style: TIPS2,方正超粗黑_GBK,40,&H00C22D01,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,,0,0,0,,——————————————STAFF——————————————
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.97,0:03:29.98,STAFF,,0,0,0,,{\fs32\an2\fad(350,350)}{\c&H1CBD77&}{\fn方正粗谭黑简体}片源{\c&HFDFCFE&} {\fn方正粗谭黑简体}山山{\fn微软雅黑} ♦ {\fn方正粗谭黑简体\3c&HE7822A&}{\c&H1CBD77&}翻译{\c&HFDFCFE&} {\fn蒙纳简超刚黑}Biscuit  {\c&HFDFCFE&\fn蒙纳简超刚黑}QB{\fn方正粗谭黑繁体\fs27}俺の嫁{\fs32\fn蒙纳简超刚黑}{\fn微软雅黑} ♦ {\fn方正粗谭黑简体}{\c&H1CBD77&}校对{\c&HFDFCFE&\fn方正粗谭黑简体} 尘焱{\fn微软雅黑} ♦ {\fn方正粗谭黑简体}{\c&H1CBD77&}后期{\c&HFDFCFE&} {\fn蒙纳简超刚黑}Rainship{\fn微软雅黑} ♦ {\c&H1CBD77&\fn方正粗谭黑简体}繁化 {\c&HFDFCFE&\fn方正粗谭黑简体}塔布里斯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.97,0:03:29.98,STAFF,,0,0,0,,{\fs32\an8\fad(350,350)\c&H1CBD77&}{\fn方正粗谭黑简体\c&H1CBD77&}澄空学园{\c&HFDFCFE&}{\fn微软雅黑} ♦ {\fn方正粗谭黑简体}华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,,0,0,0,,——————————————Tittle——————————————
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.06,0:03:34.94,Tittle,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(290,364)\fad(800,0)}谁是说谎者
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.06,0:03:34.94,TittleN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fs30\fn方正小标宋_GBK\fad(800,0)\pos(861.259,607.949)}未来篇 #0{\c&H0604F5&}4
Comment: 0,0:02:01.22,0:02:01.26,*Default,,0,0,0,,——————————————OPJP——————————————
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.22,0:02:06.02,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,STAND UP まだ僕を呼んでる声が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.02,0:02:11.48,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,「YES」だって「NO」だって 関係はないさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.48,0:02:16.24,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,STARDUST 穴だらけのゲームスコア
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.24,0:02:21.66,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,DEAD OR LIE DEAD OR LIE　自由を見たくて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.66,0:02:26.37,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,GO OUT 閉ざされた夜に I'll be eaten away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.37,0:02:31.71,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,透明な武器を手に入れてる LIAR
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.71,0:02:36.88,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,なんの為に　何を守る　長い待ちは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.88,0:02:41.51,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,ぶち壞すこの彈丸で！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.51,0:02:46.68,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,NEVER LIE モノクロな光のない世界でも
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.68,0:02:51.60,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,NEVER END NEVER LIE　心は染まらない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.60,0:02:57.44,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,THE END OF WORLD　絕望に僅かな希望握りしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.44,0:03:06.37,OPJP,NTP,0,0,0,,震える指で狙い定めて 未來を探せ！
Comment: 0,0:02:01.22,0:02:01.26,*Default,,0,0,0,,——————————————OPCN——————————————
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.22,0:02:06.02,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,STAND UP 呼唤我的声音未绝于耳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.02,0:02:11.48,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,无论答案是「YES」或「NO」 都没什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.48,0:02:16.24,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,STARDUST 游戏结果已满是漏洞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.24,0:02:21.66,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,DEAD OR LIE DEAD OR LIE 希冀能看到自由
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.66,0:02:26.37,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,GO OUT 在这憋闷的夜晚 我终将被腐蚀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.37,0:02:31.71,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,无形的武器已然到手 LIAR
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.71,0:02:36.88,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,是为了什么 要守护什么 才经过漫长等待
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.88,0:02:41.51,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,就用这颗子弹破坏一切！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.51,0:02:46.68,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,NEVER LIE 即使在这仅剩黑白 暗无光辉的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.68,0:02:51.60,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,NEVER END NEVER LIE 心灵绝不沾染黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.60,0:02:57.44,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,THE END OF WORLD 在绝望中握住仅存的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.44,0:03:06.37,OPCN,NTP,0,0,0,,用颤抖的手指瞄准目标 去追寻未来！
Comment: 0,0:22:25.19,0:22:25.24,*Default,,0,0,0,,——————————————EDJP——————————————
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.53,0:22:35.75,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}終わりが始まるアリアと共に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.75,0:22:40.42,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}白旗を掲げた奇跡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.92,0:22:46.17,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}脱獄の果てに歓声の中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.17,0:22:50.34,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}手錠突き付けられ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.80,0:22:56.22,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}ほら、見て　愚かな駒よ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.22,0:23:01.27,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}断罪の茶番
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.35,0:23:04.02,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}独壇場Funky
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.02,0:23:06.69,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}その目で見ろ　競争
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.74,0:23:11.78,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}{\fad(200,200)}Forget
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.69,0:23:11.78,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}欺いてよ　Close Enough
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.78,0:23:14.37,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}多発的な展開
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.37,0:23:17.16,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}人の波を掻き分け
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.16,0:23:19.87,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}叫べ　My Justice，Right Way
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.87,0:23:22.25,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}Make it a vow!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.25,0:23:24.88,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}感心できるのはFunky
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.88,0:23:27.59,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}喪失だけが拒止
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.59,0:23:32.59,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}導いてよ　Close Enough
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.64,0:23:35.26,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}鮮烈過ぎた年回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.35,0:23:37.43,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}偏見のあるカテゴライズ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.43,0:23:39.64,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}Don't believe no story
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.64,0:23:41.69,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}I know you're ready
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.69,0:23:43.56,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}No, we're already over
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.56,0:23:45.57,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}Everybody loves despair
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.57,0:23:48.99,EDJP,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}I'll sadly go from the end
Comment: 0,0:22:25.19,0:22:25.24,*Default,,0,0,0,,——————————————EDCN——————————————
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.53,0:22:35.75,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}伴随着结尾即开始的咏叹调
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.75,0:22:40.42,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}高举白旗的奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.92,0:22:46.17,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}在逃狱后的欢呼声中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.17,0:22:50.34,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}被强行拷上了手铐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.80,0:22:56.22,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}看吧 愚昧的棋子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.22,0:23:01.27,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}这定罪的把戏
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.35,0:23:04.02,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}奇异的独角戏舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.02,0:23:06.69,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}用你的眼睛看着 竞争
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.74,0:23:11.78,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}{\fad(200,200)}遗落
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.69,0:23:11.78,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}欺骗吧 Close Enough
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.78,0:23:14.37,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}多线并行的发展
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.37,0:23:17.16,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}拨开人群
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.16,0:23:19.87,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}呼喊着 这是我正义的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.87,0:23:22.25,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}许下你的誓言
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.25,0:23:24.88,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}值得赞美的惊恐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.88,0:23:27.59,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}唯独拒绝丧失
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.59,0:23:32.59,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}指引我吧 Close Enough
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.64,0:23:35.26,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}过于艳丽的忌日
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.35,0:23:37.43,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}带有偏见的分类
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.43,0:23:39.64,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}不要相信没有故事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.64,0:23:41.69,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}我知道你准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.69,0:23:43.56,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}不 我们已经结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.56,0:23:45.57,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}人人都爱着绝望
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.57,0:23:48.99,EDCN,NTP,0,0,0,,{\blur5}我会满怀悲伤地离去
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,,0,0,0,,——————————————TIPS——————————————
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.85,0:01:26.52,TIPS2,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(250,0)\move(840,604,125,604,23,4653)\clip(m 185 528 l 155 646 69 648 71 661 124 662 141 679 150 629 166 636 183 644 195 648 1252 640 1236 521 1268 440)}叶隐被排除在外，望周知。
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,,0,0,0,,——————————————SUB——————————————
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.35,0:00:07.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,动画都放了三集了  各位都有在看吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.65,0:00:11.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是《弹丸论破3》的前情回顾哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.40,0:00:16.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,苗木诚被叫到了未来机关的设施里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.87,0:00:20.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里是未来机关的副会长
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.66,0:00:24.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宗方京助所造的建筑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.62,0:00:29.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,话说燃烧着歼灭绝望之心的副会长
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.34,0:00:31.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真是魄力十足啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.01,0:00:34.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后  苗木在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.63,0:00:40.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因庇护绝望残党的罪名而被问罪  但这时…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.47,0:00:43.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哇  这里被人袭击了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.48,0:00:46.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这种过分的事究竟是谁做的？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.60,0:00:50.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后他们之间就展开了相互残杀的游戏！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.53,0:00:55.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来一起阻止混入未来机关的叛徒——袭击者吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.20,0:01:00.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,若在睡着时被杀  就意味着Game  over！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.41,0:01:05.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,触发了设定的NG行动也会Game  over！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.96,0:01:08.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把可疑的家伙宰个精光吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.42,0:01:14.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果在时限结束醒来后谁都没死的话  就表示通关了！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.55,0:01:19.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\clip(m 301 684 l 347 694 385 703 408 707 436 713 460 717 795 716 834 711 861 706 894 700 943 688 982 677 1020 666 1069 648 1102 633 1082 538 184 540 160 635 215 656 260 671)}明明这么简单的游戏  都死三个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.72,0:01:22.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,剩余成员还有12人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.31,0:01:26.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\clip(m 303 686 l 352 699 385 705 408 709 436 715 460 719 795 718 836 713 861 708 895 702 941 690 982 679 1020 668 1069 650 1102 635 1082 540 184 542 160 637 215 658 260 673)}互相残杀的游戏也渐入佳境了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.95,0:01:43.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\clip(m 303 686 l 352 699 385 705 408 709 436 715 460 719 795 718 836 713 861 708 895 702 941 690 982 679 1020 668 1069 650 1102 635 1082 540 184 542 160 637 215 658 260 673)}最后能够存活下来的究竟会是谁呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.58,0:01:47.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那么  下一个死的会是谁呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.00,0:01:49.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唔噗噗噗噗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.99,0:03:47.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,突然把椅子扔过来  真危险啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.29,0:03:53.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果苗木诚是绝望残党
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.08,0:03:57.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,作为同伴的她就一定是共犯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.75,0:03:59.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把她交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.01,0:04:02.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,稍安勿躁  逆藏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.09,0:04:06.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会长的架势你还要摆到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.68,0:04:08.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可是宗方的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.10,0:04:12.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没理由服从你的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.02,0:04:15.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,切
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.32,0:04:22.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会长…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.08,0:04:31.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.91,0:04:32.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,滚开
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.40,0:04:59.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太好了  这样一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.03,0:05:06.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.07,0:05:07.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这该死的怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.91,0:05:13.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.12,0:05:15.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是爆炸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.75,0:05:17.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.09,0:05:22.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哇  功能齐全啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.80,0:05:26.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不对…等等我  月光原同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.77,0:05:37.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,刚才那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.07,0:05:42.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真不赖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.61,0:05:52.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,未来机关的会长可非易与之物
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.63,0:06:09.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么  不打我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.51,0:06:13.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你原来不是超高校级的拳击手么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.58,0:06:38.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这把老骨头还真不太吃得消啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.55,0:06:48.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样他就不会追来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.05,0:06:51.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但愿如此
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.93,0:06:53.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小响！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.85,0:07:00.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,幸好你没事！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.31,0:07:04.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯  幸好你也没事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.11,0:07:06.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小响你受伤了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.32,0:07:08.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小伤而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.28,0:07:13.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  都是因为我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.20,0:07:18.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我总是…总是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.29,0:07:21.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明明想要帮助大伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.50,0:07:24.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,却让大伙陷入不幸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.30,0:07:28.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁也救不了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.01,0:07:31.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么我没法成为苗木那样的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.59,0:07:34.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就是你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.64,0:07:36.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有必要成为苗木
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.81,0:07:42.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  而且你不是还救了我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.73,0:07:44.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是我的救命恩人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.44,0:07:48.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  怎么能对女生暴力相向
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.73,0:07:50.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说的是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.61,0:07:52.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好疼！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.57,0:07:57.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,救命恩人…言过其实了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.83,0:08:03.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你救过我们两个是不争的事实
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.80,0:08:09.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你们…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.97,0:08:12.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全馆通告
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.22,0:08:16.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全馆通告
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.26,0:08:17.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.30,0:08:18.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是宗方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.43,0:08:20.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在刚才
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.73,0:08:23.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已将苗木诚捕获
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.06,0:08:26.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,捕获了苗木？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.86,0:08:31.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在将对苗木进行处刑
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.32,0:08:34.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,处刑苗木？怎…怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.57,0:08:35.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.70,0:08:36.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,陷阱？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.66,0:08:40.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他打算将苗木作为诱饵引诱我们上钩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.08,0:08:43.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那怎么办才好？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.71,0:08:45.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,苗木会被杀的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.21,0:08:47.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去他那里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.42,0:08:52.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,既然他还没杀苗木  应该是抱着什么意图
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.97,0:08:55.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有谈判的余地
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.05,0:08:57.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.31,0:09:03.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谈判的话  让老夫去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.74,0:09:20.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,醒了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.54,0:09:24.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你打算怎么处置我？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.75,0:09:27.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就是个诱饵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.79,0:09:31.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我为了那些想要救你的人所准备的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.71,0:09:32.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诱饵？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.34,0:09:34.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的目的不是杀我…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.76,0:09:37.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是袭击者  这点我还是明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.43,0:09:39.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.97,0:09:42.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你认为这次自相残杀中可能发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.52,0:09:45.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最为恐怖的结局是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.94,0:09:49.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那当然是我们被袭击者杀光
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.27,0:09:50.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全军覆没的结局了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.77,0:09:51.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.65,0:09:57.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,假如我死后袭击突然停止了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.53,0:09:58.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,将会怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.37,0:10:03.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就说明宗方你是袭击者吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.20,0:10:06.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一般情况是会这样想的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.46,0:10:09.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但却没有确认的手段
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.96,0:10:13.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,原来是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.25,0:10:16.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,袭击者可以随时中止这场游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.22,0:10:22.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,袭击者只要找个替身杀了  然后结束游戏的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.51,0:10:29.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这家伙接下来就可以轻而易举地潜伏在未来机关之中
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.15,0:10:32.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,作为自相残杀游戏中存活下来的英雄…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.52,0:10:38.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后  成为了英雄的袭击者就能够控制未来机关
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.41,0:10:42.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要同样作为一起存活下来的你还在
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.87,0:10:45.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的控制就会越发地稳如磐石
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.54,0:10:48.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,袭击者会利用你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.04,0:10:50.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,披上希望的外衣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.13,0:10:53.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,深深埋下绝望的根源
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.84,0:10:58.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,披着希望外皮的绝望传遍世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.30,0:11:01.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那样的结局才是最糟糕的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.34,0:11:03.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.47,0:11:06.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对袭击者来说我是尤为重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.39,0:11:09.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你想将我作为诱饵引他出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.39,0:11:12.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.44,0:11:13.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因此…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.02,0:11:16.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不论是你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.86,0:11:19.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是要利用你的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.28,0:11:22.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都不能活在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.03,0:11:27.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这么说的话  我们不是只能全军覆没了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.54,0:11:30.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别小看未来机关
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.83,0:11:35.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哪怕我们在这里全军覆没
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.63,0:11:38.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,由我所整顿的未来机关也不会动摇
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.63,0:11:42.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为这不算是希望
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.26,0:11:47.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,难道你没做出任何牺牲就战胜了江之岛盾子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.64,0:11:54.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的希望能够打动人心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.69,0:11:59.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但现在的你就有如无法控制的炸弹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.89,0:12:33.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要交涉的话就由老夫去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.85,0:12:34.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会长
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.40,0:12:38.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正好我也有话想跟宗方君说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.23,0:12:41.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,毕竟是老相识了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.32,0:12:42.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.45,0:12:46.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是会长的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.45,0:12:49.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而你  不还有唯有你才能解决的是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.33,0:12:55.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道了  苗木的事就拜托您了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.37,0:12:57.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我跟会长一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.96,0:13:02.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经把路线替你们查好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.43,0:13:05.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,御手洗君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.09,0:13:06.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.05,0:13:12.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你来护送雾切君  她的脚受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.73,0:13:14.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我…我会加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.06,0:13:19.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那么  老夫也该去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.91,0:13:28.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.74,0:13:34.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你来啦  小雾切  是来查证现场吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.66,0:13:35.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么你会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.96,0:13:40.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个嘛  这种时候最安全的地方当然是侦探身边啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.46,0:13:43.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,啊  疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.64,0:13:54.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爱情使人发狂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.14,0:13:58.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪染君去世之后  你就失去镇静了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.36,0:14:05.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,袖中箭  居然使这么一件老古董
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.28,0:14:07.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,朝日奈君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.65,0:14:08.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.28,0:14:11.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,苗木
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.21,0:14:20.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会长
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.83,0:14:24.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就这样  把他带回安全的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.05,0:14:25.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.55,0:14:26.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,苗木君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.17,0:14:27.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.26,0:14:32.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我坚信你是「超高校级的希望」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.72,0:14:39.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,苗木君  之后的事就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.15,0:14:41.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.98,0:14:46.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,担心什么  我只是想跟宗方君谈谈而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.32,0:14:48.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天愿先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.20,0:14:49.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.79,0:15:01.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个  我能问个问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.17,0:15:08.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你对发起这场残杀游戏的人有什么想法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.51,0:15:11.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前的情报还太少
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.72,0:15:15.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先入为主的观念会妨碍推理
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.56,0:15:17.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.10,0:15:19.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.77,0:15:23.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你应该是有一些想法的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.36,0:15:27.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以才会在意别人怎么想  不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.94,0:15:30.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.67,0:15:45.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,苗木诚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.51,0:15:55.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宗方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.89,0:15:56.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是逆藏吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.22,0:15:58.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.47,0:15:59.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.68,0:16:00.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.98,0:16:02.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快去追苗木诚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.98,0:16:05.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.52,0:16:08.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.99,0:16:16.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.00,0:16:29.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,流流歌
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.13,0:16:33.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你先逃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.51,0:16:36.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小夜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.27,0:16:48.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别  别再这样了  静子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.32,0:16:50.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以前我们的关系不是很好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.94,0:16:54.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事到如今  你还说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.86,0:16:59.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是因为你们  我才会被希望峰学园劝退
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.75,0:17:03.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别说了  快逃  流流歌
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.00,0:17:06.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你打算只顾自己跑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.92,0:17:10.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,果然你才是叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.34,0:17:13.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,叛徒是你才对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.01,0:17:17.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜你所赐  我和流流歌都受到了退学处分
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.93,0:17:20.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道在那之后我们有多辛苦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.68,0:17:25.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们才是叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.23,0:17:28.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.27,0:17:30.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯  小夜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.63,0:17:50.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别想跑
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.31,0:18:03.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还嫩了点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.57,0:18:14.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,年轻人总以为只要激进
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.07,0:18:16.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就能与现实抗争
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.03,0:18:21.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是在我看来  那才是天真的做法
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.49,0:18:25.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正是这种天真造成了牺牲
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.79,0:18:27.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管会有多少牺牲
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.12,0:18:31.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那都是歼灭绝望所必要的牺牲
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.04,0:18:36.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,原来如此  这就是说雪染君也算必要的牺牲吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.80,0:18:44.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说过  你还太嫩了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.28,0:19:06.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到这里  应该能放心了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.45,0:19:08.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.33,0:19:09.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你道什么歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.21,0:19:12.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.30,0:19:17.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人追过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.55,0:19:21.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.43,0:19:23.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么啊  那太乱来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.01,0:19:26.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你突然是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.85,0:19:31.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大概我被苗木的希望感染了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.06,0:19:34.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等…等等
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.69,0:19:40.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管怎么说  你们的NG类型都不适合战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.36,0:19:43.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里只能交给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.74,0:19:47.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等到全部结束之后  一起吃甜甜圈哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.24,0:19:48.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就这么约定了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.41,0:19:52.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一定会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.31,0:20:12.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开火！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.84,0:20:41.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你笑什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.68,0:20:45.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,老夫是笑我这副模样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.05,0:20:50.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看来还是你运气好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.64,0:20:56.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直以为你的意志已经腐朽了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.61,0:20:59.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我才不得不背负一切
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.32,0:21:05.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就算把你杀了也…  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.24,0:21:07.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.82,0:21:09.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我改变主意了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.08,0:21:12.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,原本以为你只是个失去锋芒的人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.70,0:21:14.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如今看来好像并非如此
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.63,0:21:18.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想知道你的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.72,0:21:25.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还真是乱来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.59,0:21:29.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真亏你能撑下来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.76,0:21:31.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但也到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.77,0:21:35.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要展示我的七个秘密兵器了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.82,0:21:43.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是第一个秘密兵器
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.90,0:21:45.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其名为……
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.61,0:21:48.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.76,0:22:10.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,咦  动不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.89,0:22:15.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不重新启动不行了吗  真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.81,0:22:18.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这还真是超级绝望的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.06,0:00:00.06,*Default,,0,0,0,,
